<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://info.linuxserver.io"/><title>lidarr on Info :: LinuxServer.io</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/lidarr/</link><description>History</description><generator>github.com/cstate</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>2022-06-05T18:00:00+00:00</lastBuildDate><updated>2022-06-05T18:00:00+00:00</updated><atom:link href="https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/lidarr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Notification: Lidarr Latest Rebase To Alpine</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-06-05-lidarr/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-06-05-lidarr/</guid><category/><description>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our Lidarr latest tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the Alpine packages and package manager (apk).</description><content type="html">&lt;p>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-lidarr">Lidarr&lt;/a> &lt;code>latest&lt;/code> tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the &lt;a href="https://pkgs.alpinelinux.org/packages?name=&amp;amp;branch=v3.15">Alpine packages&lt;/a> and package manager (&lt;code>apk&lt;/code>).&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Notification: Lidarr Develop Rebase To Alpine</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-02-18-lidarr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-02-18-lidarr/</guid><category/><description>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our Lidarr develop tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the Alpine packages and package manager (apk).</description><content type="html">&lt;p>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-lidarr">Lidarr&lt;/a> &lt;code>develop&lt;/code> tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the &lt;a href="https://pkgs.alpinelinux.org/packages?name=&amp;amp;branch=v3.15">Alpine packages&lt;/a> and package manager (&lt;code>apk&lt;/code>).&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Notification: Lidarr Nightly Rebase To Alpine</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-02-03-lidarr/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-02-03-lidarr/</guid><category/><description>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our Lidarr nightly tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the Alpine packages and package manager (apk).</description><content type="html">&lt;p>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-lidarr">Lidarr&lt;/a> &lt;code>nightly&lt;/code> tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the &lt;a href="https://pkgs.alpinelinux.org/packages?name=&amp;amp;branch=v3.15">Alpine packages&lt;/a> and package manager (&lt;code>apk&lt;/code>).&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>New Container: Lidarr</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2018-02-23-lidarr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2018-02-23-lidarr/</guid><category/><description>We have released a new container for Lidarr!
Lidarr is a music collection manager for Usenet and BitTorrent users. It can monitor multiple RSS feeds for new tracks from your favorite artists and will grab, sort and rename them. It can also be configured to automatically upgrade the quality of files already downloaded when a better quality format becomes available.</description><content type="html">&lt;p>We have released a new container for &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-lidarr">Lidarr&lt;/a>!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/lidarr/Lidarr">Lidarr&lt;/a> is a music collection manager for Usenet and BitTorrent users. It can monitor multiple RSS feeds for new tracks from your favorite artists and will grab, sort and rename them. It can also be configured to automatically upgrade the quality of files already downloaded when a better quality format becomes available.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>