<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://info.linuxserver.io"/><title>synology on Info :: LinuxServer.io</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/synology/</link><description>History</description><generator>github.com/cstate</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>2023-12-30T18:00:00+00:00</lastBuildDate><updated>2023-12-30T18:00:00+00:00</updated><atom:link href="https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/synology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[Resolved] Known Issue: curl endless loop with 3.x Kernels</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2023-12-30-synology/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2023-12-30-synology/</guid><category>2024-01-12 12:00:00Z</category><description>Update The Alpine maintainers have backported a fixed version of the affected library to 3.19 and we have published a new version of our 3.19 base image that should resolve the issues with 3.x kernels. It will take a few days for all affected downstream images to push new builds, but any image released from this point onwards will include the fix.
Original Post There is a known issue with the version of curl currently shipped with Alpine 3.</description><content type="html">&lt;h2 id="update">Update&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Alpine maintainers have backported a fixed version of the affected library to 3.19 and we have published a new version of our 3.19 base image that should resolve the issues with 3.x kernels. It will take a few days for all affected downstream images to push new builds, but any image released from this point onwards will include the fix.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="original-post">Original Post&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>There is a known issue with the version of curl currently shipped with Alpine 3.19 and 3.x kernels, causing an endless loop to hang containers, usually on startup. The 3.x kernel line has been End of Life since 2017, but some prebuilt systems such as older Synology NAS units are still running it. At time of posting, around 10% of our images have already been rebased to Alpine 3.19 and are therefore affected by this issue, and this number will continue to rise over the next few months.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>While a fix has been applied to the affected upstream library we do not have an ETA for if or when it will find its way into the version of curl shipped with Alpine 3.19.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="workaround">Workaround&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>As a workaround you can revert to an older tag from before the image was rebased to Alpine 3.19, but please be aware that older tags do not receive updates. Refer to the Changelog in the Readme to see when the change was made for a given image. For Unraid users this will require you to edit the container and under the Advanced options change the Repository to append the required tag.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>[Resolved] Known Issue: Portainer &amp; Synology Docker UI</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2023-05-22-portainer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2023-05-22-portainer/</guid><category>2023-11-22 18:00:00Z</category><description>Update The underlying issue still exists for both Portainer and the Synology container management UI, but the primary driver of issues has largely dissipated and so we are unpinning this notice.
Original Post There is a known issue with Portainer and the Synology Docker UI when updating (or otherwise recreating) containers, which causes them to overwrite settings in the new image with values from the old container. Creating a new container from scratch does not exhibit this behaviour.</description><content type="html">&lt;h3 id="update">Update&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The underlying issue still exists for both Portainer and the Synology container management UI, but the primary driver of issues has largely dissipated and so we are unpinning this notice.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="original-post">Original Post&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>There is a known issue with Portainer and the Synology Docker UI when updating (or otherwise recreating) containers, which causes them to overwrite settings in the new image with values from the old container. Creating a new container from scratch does not exhibit this behaviour.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This non-standard behaviour causes containers to fail to start correctly in some cases, and may result in unexpected or unwanted configuration in others. For example, in our &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-sabnzbd/issues/188">SABnzbd image&lt;/a> the &lt;code>PATH&lt;/code> environment variable is overwritten, leaving the application unable to locate the necessary Python modules to enable it to start. This is likely to become more common in the future, and there is not a practical or scalable solution that we can apply from our end to avoid this issue.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Our position remains that we provide support only for containers created and updated using Docker Compose, the Docker CLI, or using our Unraid templates, and not any 3rd party tools.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>