<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://info.linuxserver.io"/><title>radarr on Info :: LinuxServer.io</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/radarr/</link><description>History</description><generator>github.com/cstate</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>2022-06-05T18:00:00+00:00</lastBuildDate><updated>2022-06-05T18:00:00+00:00</updated><atom:link href="https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/radarr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Notification: Radarr Latest Rebase To Alpine</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-06-05-radarr/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-06-05-radarr/</guid><category/><description>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our Radarr latest tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the Alpine packages and package manager (apk).</description><content type="html">&lt;p>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-radarr">Radarr&lt;/a> &lt;code>latest&lt;/code> tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the &lt;a href="https://pkgs.alpinelinux.org/packages?name=&amp;amp;branch=v3.15">Alpine packages&lt;/a> and package manager (&lt;code>apk&lt;/code>).&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Notification: Radarr Develop Rebase To Alpine</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-02-18-radarr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-02-18-radarr/</guid><category/><description>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our Radarr develop tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the Alpine packages and package manager (apk).</description><content type="html">&lt;p>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-radarr">Radarr&lt;/a> &lt;code>develop&lt;/code> tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the &lt;a href="https://pkgs.alpinelinux.org/packages?name=&amp;amp;branch=v3.15">Alpine packages&lt;/a> and package manager (&lt;code>apk&lt;/code>).&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Notification: Radarr Nightly Rebase To Alpine</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-02-03-radarr/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2022-02-03-radarr/</guid><category/><description>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our Radarr nightly tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the Alpine packages and package manager (apk).</description><content type="html">&lt;p>For operational reasons we will shortly be rebasing our &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-radarr">Radarr&lt;/a> &lt;code>nightly&lt;/code> tag to use our Alpine base image. If you use the image as-is this will not have any direct impact, however, if you make use of any customization scripts which install additional packages these may need to be updated to use the &lt;a href="https://pkgs.alpinelinux.org/packages?name=&amp;amp;branch=v3.15">Alpine packages&lt;/a> and package manager (&lt;code>apk&lt;/code>).&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>New Container: Radarr</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2017-01-10-radarr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2017-01-10-radarr/</guid><category/><description>We have released a new container for Radarr!
Radarr - A fork of Sonarr to work with movies à la Couchpotato.</description><content type="html">&lt;p>We have released a new container for &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-radarr">Radarr&lt;/a>!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/Radarr/Radarr">Radarr&lt;/a> - A fork of Sonarr to work with movies à la Couchpotato.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>