<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://info.linuxserver.io"/><title>wireguard on Info :: LinuxServer.io</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/wireguard/</link><description>History</description><generator>github.com/cstate</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>2023-04-27T12:00:00+00:00</lastBuildDate><updated>2023-04-27T12:00:00+00:00</updated><atom:link href="https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/wireguard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Notification: Changes to Wireguard image tags</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2023-04-27-wireguard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2023-04-27-wireguard/</guid><category/><description>We will shortly be making changes to the tags available for our Wireguard image.
Currently we offer two tags: latest and alpine. The former uses our Ubuntu base image and contains all of the tools and dependencies required to compile the Wireguard kernel modules from scratch if your host kernel is too old to have it built-in. The latter uses our Alpine base image and does not contain the build tools and dependencies, which means it will only work on hosts that already have the Wireguard kernel modules installed and running.</description><content type="html">&lt;p>We will shortly be making changes to the tags available for our &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-wireguard">Wireguard&lt;/a> image.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Currently we offer two tags: &lt;code>latest&lt;/code> and &lt;code>alpine&lt;/code>. The former uses our Ubuntu base image and contains all of the tools and dependencies required to compile the Wireguard kernel modules from scratch if your host kernel is too old to have it built-in. The latter uses our Alpine base image and does &lt;em>not&lt;/em> contain the build tools and dependencies, which means it will only work on hosts that already have the Wireguard kernel modules installed and running.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Almost all kernel builds since 5.6 come with Wireguard included, along with some older ones that have had it backported, which means that shipping an extra 800Mb of image by default to support those running old kernels is increasingly unnecessary.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a result, we&amp;rsquo;re going to switch our tags around to make the Alpine-based image the default.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using the &lt;code>latest&lt;/code> tag you&amp;rsquo;ll soon automatically get switched to the Alpine-based build.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using the &lt;code>alpine&lt;/code> tag you&amp;rsquo;ll need to switch to &lt;code>latest&lt;/code> to continue receiving updates.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If you&amp;rsquo;re still running an old kernel and need the build support, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to switch to the &lt;code>legacy&lt;/code> tag.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></content></item><item><title>New Container: Wireguard</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2020-03-31-wireguard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2020-03-31-wireguard/</guid><category/><description>We have released a new container for Wireguard!
WireGuard® is an extremely simple yet fast and modern VPN that utilizes state-of-the-art cryptography. It aims to be faster, simpler, leaner, and more useful than IPsec, while avoiding the massive headache. It intends to be considerably more performant than OpenVPN. WireGuard is designed as a general purpose VPN for running on embedded interfaces and super computers alike, fit for many different circumstances. Initially released for the Linux kernel, it is now cross-platform (Windows, macOS, BSD, iOS, Android) and widely deployable.</description><content type="html">&lt;p>We have released a new container for &lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-wireguard">Wireguard&lt;/a>!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.wireguard.com/">WireGuard®&lt;/a> is an extremely simple yet fast and modern VPN that utilizes state-of-the-art cryptography. It aims to be faster, simpler, leaner, and more useful than IPsec, while avoiding the massive headache. It intends to be considerably more performant than OpenVPN. WireGuard is designed as a general purpose VPN for running on embedded interfaces and super computers alike, fit for many different circumstances. Initially released for the Linux kernel, it is now cross-platform (Windows, macOS, BSD, iOS, Android) and widely deployable. It is currently under heavy development, but already it might be regarded as the most secure, easiest to use, and simplest VPN solution in the industry.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>