<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://info.linuxserver.io"/><title>librewolf on Info :: LinuxServer.io</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/librewolf/</link><description>History</description><generator>github.com/cstate</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>2024-04-13T20:00:00+00:00</lastBuildDate><updated>2024-04-13T20:00:00+00:00</updated><atom:link href="https://info.linuxserver.io/affected/librewolf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Containers: FreeTube Librewolf Ardour KeePassXC</title><link>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2024-04-13-freetube-keepassxc-ardour-librewolf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.linuxserver.io/issues/2024-04-13-freetube-keepassxc-ardour-librewolf/</guid><category/><description>We have released new desktop application containers for: Ardour Librewolf FreeTube KeePassXC
Ardour is an open source, collaborative effort of a worldwide team including musicians, programmers, and professional recording engineers. LibreWolf is a custom and independent version of Firefox, with the primary goals of privacy, security and user freedom. FreeTube is a feature-rich and user-friendly YouTube client with a focus on privacy. KeePassXC is a free and open-source password manager. It started as a community fork of KeePassX (itself a cross-platform port of KeePass).</description><content type="html">&lt;p>We have released new desktop application containers for:
&lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-ardour/">Ardour&lt;/a>
&lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-librewolf/">Librewolf&lt;/a>
&lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-freetube/">FreeTube&lt;/a>
&lt;a href="https://github.com/linuxserver/docker-keepassxc/">KeePassXC&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://ardour.org/">Ardour&lt;/a> is an open source, collaborative effort of a worldwide team including musicians, programmers, and professional recording engineers.
&lt;a href="https://librewolf.net/">LibreWolf&lt;/a> is a custom and independent version of Firefox, with the primary goals of privacy, security and user freedom.
&lt;a href="https://freetubeapp.io/">FreeTube&lt;/a> is a feature-rich and user-friendly YouTube client with a focus on privacy.
&lt;a href="https://keepassxc.org/">KeePassXC&lt;/a> is a free and open-source password manager. It started as a community fork of KeePassX (itself a cross-platform port of KeePass).&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>